Good evening , this is Angela Vidal speaking .
Tonight , as usual ,
we will share this time ...
Just a second ...
- Where does the shot cut ? - Down here .
Down here ? You can 't see my ... This hand , right ?
- No . - OK .
Wait , out .
Good evening , this is Angela Vidal speaking .
Today on " While You 're Asleep " we are accompanying a team of firemen
on their nightly rounds .
I 'm out of breath ...
Good evening , this is Angela Vidal speaking .
Tonight on " While You 're Asleep " we 'll accompany a team of firemen
on their rounds through the city .
Not only that , but we 'll see things never before revealed :
how they live , sleep , what they eat ...
We 'll get an inside look at this fire station .
Join us for " While You 're Asleep . "
- OK . - OK ?
If this is a pain in the ass , just cut , OK ?
I don 't want to waste the tape .
Andreu , you 're the boss , right ?
The organizer ...
Yes , I 'm in charge of this shift ,
both inside the fire house and out fighting fires .
This is our helmet . It 's a full face helmet .
You can put it on , it 's clean .
I 'm going to be the heroine of " While You 're Asleep " .
Should we put them on ?
It 's easy . You 're all so huge , aren 't you ?
We 're big , yes . These are the boots .
Our pants are inside the boots .
Like in the cartoons , right ? You jump right in them !
The cartoons copied us , not the other way around .
I 'm a firefighter .
Well , let 's see if ...
- if there 's a call . - Yeah .
Will you let me go with you ?
- Of course . - OK .
- It 's like a lottery . - A what ?
A lottery .
We might get a call , we might not .
We 'll see if we do ...
You 'll see , I 'll help you out .
- Perfect . - OK .
We 're going to the dining room . It 's dinner time .
- Will they mind if I come in ? - No , not at all .
- They know you 're here . - We can try that
that delicious food that firemen make .
- Exactly . Very good . - Let 's go .
Be careful ! You 'll hurt yourself .
- Let 's go to the dining room . - This way .
Hello .
- Bon appétit ! - Thanks !
Enjoy your meal .
This is Manu and Alex , they will join you this evening .
Nice to meet you . Please , keep eating . My name 's Angela .
We 'll accompany you tonight .
Finish eating , we 'll see you later .
- Do you want to go to the museum ? - Yes , after you .
Turn around .
I think I 'll put it in your pocket .
Won 't it bother you when you put on your belt ?
I don 't think so . If it does , we can move it .
Here you have to do everything .
- Let 's see ... - Is this right ?
- Say something . - One , two ...
- Hello , hello ... - OK , keep going .
A little more .
Hello , my name is Manu and tonight the TV is here .
- We 'll have fun ... I don 't know . - OK .
- Ready ? - A tiny step to your right .
You know what ? I 'm going to change sides .
- If you don 't mind . It 's my hair . - You 're here ?
So , Alex , tell us what a normal night is like
here in the fire house .
A normal night is pretty monotonous because ...
- Normal ? - Yes , normal .
People think we run around
putting out fires , but
around 70 % of the calls we get
are for other types of services .
- Like what ? - For example ,
broken water mains ,
or pet rescue , too .
I know it sounds clichéd but it 's true .
Or to ...
This will sound terrible , but I 'd love the alarm to ring now
and everyone to run off .
- I don 't want anything to happen . - Let 's hope not .
I mean , just to go with you , to see what your real work is like .
- Don 't get me wrong . - No , no . I understand .
- It 's more interesting for you . - So we can show it .
It 's more exciting ... Let 's hope nothing happens .
That everything is fine and nothing happens .
- A routine call , right ? - Exactly .
So , that 's a fireman 's life .
Waiting , passing time .
Watching movies
- in the living room , right , Alex ? - Let 's go there .
OK .
This is boring .
What should we do ? Should we go to reception ?
- All right . - OK ?
We should do something , right ?
How exciting !
OK .
- Hello . Can I come in ? - Good evening .
Finally ! Women in the fire station .
Where are you going ?
- I 'm sorry ... - Don 't be embarrassed .
Time 's going by
and it gets quieter . There 's no one here .
The dining room is empty .
Boy , are they clean !
Here they 're sleeping .
When the alarm rings ,
they jump out of bed
and slide down here .
The fire trucks are down there .
We saw them before .
It takes them less than 3 minutes
to get up .
- We 'll finish this later . - We were winning !
Person trapped in apartment , in need of rescue .
Bravo 128 take the call .
What 'll we do ?
I can 't slide down with the camera .
Let 's go that way . Run .
It 's all ready . They 're really fast .
You back there . On the other side .
I don 't know if I can ...
It 's stuck .
- Let 's go . - Let 's go .
Move your legs faster ! One , two , one , two ...
Jose 's driving .
Alex and Manu are the firemen
we will accompany this evening .
We 're going to follow them , and as we 've seen
it 's not always fires that get them all moving ,
because the entire team goes out .
Even if it 's stopping
a water leak , or helping someone out of their apartment ,
or a fire ...
Don 't you put on the ...
what 's it called ... the alarm ?
We don 't normally use it for services like these
because it 's not urgent .
But if you want , we can put it on , no problem .
- What do you think ? - No , I don 't think so .
No ? Well ...
What 's your show called ?
" While You 're Asleep " .
" While You 're Asleep " ? Then who watches it ?
We have to do another take . I said alarm , not siren .
Did it make sense ? Alarm ...
- Ready ? Come on . - Let 's go .
Let 's go .
- What are you taking with you ? - Tools . We have everything
here in this case , tools
to open locks and doors .
We 're here with Alex and Manu .
We 're almost at
the house that called for help .
The police are here .
We can see a police car .
Maybe it 's more serious than we thought .
- We 'll find out soon . - No , I don 't think it is .
Let 's go in .
Good evening .
Don 't worry .
A woman was screaming .
We were called so we came over .
Please calm down .
- Screams ? Noises ? - She lives alone with her cats .
- Did you make the call ? - No .
It was me .
- It was you ? - Yes .
I heard screams so I called the police .
Let 's go . She 's upstairs .
Let 's go upstairs .
It 's about time .
We got a call and came over .
OK , this way please .
- What the hell is this ? - A local TV crew .
Please , stay here .
Sure , we 'll sleep here if you want .
Miss , miss !
Please let us work , OK ?
- They aren 't yours , are they ? - No , they 're from a local TV station .
They 're doing a report on how we work
- so they came with us . - They 're your responsibility .
Ladies and gentlemen !
Please stay in the hall .
Am I speaking Greek or what ?
If I tell you to stop , you stop taping .
If I tell you to get lost , you get lost . Got it ?
Ok . But we have permission .
The old lady lives on the first floor .
What happened ?
It looks like she fell .
They heard her scream and called ...
What about those people downstairs ?
She was screaming bloody murder .
The neighbours say she 's really weird .
She never goes out , has no family ...
Please , can you go with them ?
Go down there .
Don 't they have anything better to do ?
Go downstairs , damn it !
- Get out of the way . - Sorry , sorry .
- What 's the camera doing here ? - They 're with the firemen .
We have permission , OK ?
I 'm going to do an introduction .
- Am I OK here ? - Yeah .
OK .
We 're in front of the door
where an elderly resident
may be in trouble . The neighbours heard screaming .
Mari Carmen , who called the fire department ...
It 's OK .
Whoa ...
Ma 'am , this is the police .
We 're here to help you . Can you hear me ?
- Turn off the camera . - I 'm sorry .
Can 't you hear the ambulance , ma 'am ?
Don 't worry . We 're going to take you to the hospital .
What 's her name ?
Conchita .
Conchita ! Don 't worry ...
Come on , come on ...
Don 't worry , the police are here .
What happened ? Is she alright ?
Shit ...
- The light , please ! - Yeah , turn off the light .
Keep rolling .
- Stop taping ! - Sorry , OK . It 's off .
Unit 341 , please send an ambulance immediately .
First floor .
OK . It 's very urgent .
The ambulance is here , don 't worry , ma 'am .
Sergio , move this , damn it .
I don 't want anyone here while we wait for the ambulance .
Fuck , she 's biting him !
Pablo , what do I do ?
Get her off him !
Holy shit ! Get him out of here !
Help ! Help !
- Stay with her , Alex ! - OK .
Help me ! Get out of the way .
Hurry , hurry .
Holy fucking shit !
Get out of the way !
Hurry ! Be careful !
- You got him ? - Yeah .
Tape everything .
OK , wait . Get up !
Pablo , don 't miss a bloody thing !
Holy shit , he 's going to bleed to death .
- You got it ? - Yeah , yeah .
Stop , stop .
We have to stop the bleeding .
Come on , quick . Here .
- I can 't ! - Press here !
What the fuck 's going on ? The light !
The light !
Quick ! The light !
Fuck , come on !
Be careful ! Cover it up !
Get out of the way .
They won 't let us out .
- Why not ? - I don 't know , they said we can 't .
This man is wounded . We have to get him out .
- We have to make a compress . - Are you a doctor ?
- I 'm an intern . - Take him over there .
Be careful with his head .
Hold him up .
Call an ambulance .
The door is blocked from outside . What the fuck is going on ?
We need an ambulance , now !
Calm down , please .
Silence , please !
Please listen .
The health authorities have decided to seal off
the building for safety reasons .
We 're working to get you out as soon as possible .
We ask for your cooperation .
The agents that are with you
will keep you posted on what to do .
Follow their instructions
and remain calm . Thank you .
- What the ... ? - Shit !
341 , 341 !
Please !
- What do you mean I can 't ... - My friend 's about to ...
We are aware of the situation . We can 't do anything for now .
We 'll keep you updated .
- Fuck ! - What did they say ?
We have to get him out of here . He 's bleeding to death !
We have to get him out of here .
What 's going on ? Why can 't we leave ?
We just can 't . Just calm down .
Please , stop taping , for fuck 's sake .
- Don 't touch the camera ! - Why not ?
Do not touch the camera !
We have to let everyone know what 's going on here !
- Fucking hell ! - Calm down .
I 'm in charge here , and I say turn it off and calm down .
Then worry about what 's going on ,
not about whether we tape or not .
Yeah . Find out what 's going on .
- Tape this ! - Please !
OK , OK ! We have to get this man out of here !
- What 's behind that shutter ? - A textile workshop .
- What do you mean ? - A textile workshop .
OK . Everyone , calm down .
- Is there a way out from there ? - Yes , through the back .
Wait a second , move over there .
- How does this thing open ? - Please !
I 'm not going to repeat this . Move over there .
- What are you doing ? - Trying to get out of here .
Wait a second !
My husband 's outside and says there are loads of cops .
They 've blocked off the street .
He was getting antibiotics for her .
Holy shit !
Alex !
No , don 't move him !
- Yes , we have to . - He has a pulse , don 't move him !
- Alex ! Alex ! - Shit !
There 's somebody upstairs !
- Don 't move him ! - Look after him .
Please , come with me .
We 're going upstairs .
Nobody move from here , OK !
And you , stop fucking recording !
I don 't care what they say , we have to tape this .
We have to show what 's happening .
- What was that ? - I don 't know , be careful .
Fuck !
It 's coming from in there .
- Be careful . - Where are they ?
Move over .
Pablo , don 't ...
- No , Pablo , come here . - Be quiet .
Pablo , come here !
What 's going on ?
What the fuck are you doing here ?
Be careful .
She 's dead .
Don 't move , ma 'am .
Ma 'am .
Don 't move !
Let 's go .
She jumped on me ...
I know , relax .
- You saw her , right ? - Yeah , I did .
- I couldn 't do anything . - Let 's go downstairs .
I know , don 't worry . Let 's go .
Fucking asshole !
- Did you get it ? - I got everything .
- Let me see it . - Don 't worry . I got it .
Fucking show it to me ! How do I have to say it ?
Get this , Pablo ! Come on !
You stay here with the wounded .
I 'm going to check the exit .
Just a second .
We have strict orders to stay in the hall .
Help me out here .
These men are dying . Fuck orders !
He 's right . You shouldn 't tell us ...
There are two dead people ,
that died violent deaths .
And two that need urgent medical attention .
The police have blocked off the area ,
they are keeping us in here , with no explanations .
So , we 're searching for another way out .
She 's getting worse .
Her fever 's gone up . She needs a doctor .
Listen up .
Do not try to leave the building .
All exits have been sealed .
A BNC protocol situation has been declared .
Shortly a health inspector will come to assess the situation .
Thank you for your cooperation .
Why are we locked in here ?
And what do they mean by a health inspector ?
- I don 't know . - What 's an BNC protocol ?
What 's a BNC protocol ? What does BNC mean ?
It 's a proceedure used
in biological , nuclear , or chemical threat situations .
What ? Nuclear ?
It 's more usual than you think .
The wounded are stable , but they won 't hang on much longer .
- We have to get them out of here . - Obviously not through here .
So , ladies , gentlemen , come this way .
No ! There 's something more to this place .
Our cells don 't work . Neither does the TV or radio .
- We 're isolated . Why ? - I don 't know why .
I can 't get through to my husband .
- And my daughter has a high fever . - What 's wrong with her ?
She has tonsilitis .
- She 's burning up . - What can I do ?
From the office we can jump down on the patio .
I 'm going with you .
Where are you going ?
- Are you sure ? - Yeah , it 's not very high up .
How are we going to get in ?
What ?
The concierge has a copy of the key .
I gave it to him . I 'm in charge of the building .
Let 's go .
There was someone else in the woman 's apartment .
What do you mean someone else ? Who ?
I don 't know . A girl .
Probably the Colombian girl . Why didn 't she come down with you ?
She 's dead .
Let 's go . Open it , quick !
This way .
It 's this way .
Let 's go .
Help me .
Fuck ...
Go back immediately , for your own safety .
No , listen !
Get back .
We 're sealing off the building .
- Ready up there ? Go ahead . - Listen !
Listen to me !
Listen ! Can you see me ?
Can you hear me ?
What are you doing there ? I told you to wait downstairs .
Remember I 'm still in charge .
- You knew about this , didn 't you ? - About what ?
That they 're sealing us in . Like hamsters !
Step back ! For your own safety .
- What the hell is this ? - You tell us !
I don 't know !
- I repeat , step back ! - You ! That 's enough !
- Why ? - Stop messing with the camera .
We have to show what 's going on .
- Don 't you get it ? - Don 't touch me .
It 's the only proof we have . Can 't you see that ?
You 're locked in here just like us . They don 't care about you either .
Shut up !
Please , go down to the workshop .
- Let 's all calm down . - Shut up !
Yes , we 're going . Put the gun down .
Remain calm .
We apologize for the inconvenience .
It is of utmost importance
that you follow the agent 's instructions .
He is in the building with you .
Do not try to leave the building .
I repeat , do not try to leave the building .
Hold this . Relax , man ...
Let 's go with the others .
I 'm really sorry .
Please , go downstairs .
- Let 's go . - Thanks .
Let me go up to my apartment .
I have sutures and bandages ...
Yes ...
It 's nearly 2 a.m. and we 're still sealed in this building that
we came to with the firemen earlier this evening ,
to assist an elderly lady who later attacked a policeman
and a fireman . They 're both in critical condition .
The police won 't let us leave and are giving us no explanations .
The neighbours are scared to death .
They want to go back home ,
they want to know what 's going on .
Guillem , do you mind if I ask you a few quick questions ?
I 've never been in such a serious situation before .
I 'm an intern . I give shots ,
take people 's blood pressure . I live in this building .
Well , the injured are in critical condition .
This is very serious .
The policeman has several bite wounds .
He 's badly injured .
What 's obvious is that
Mrs. lzquierdo attacked and bit them .
I guess
she had a fit of hysteria .
But honestly , it 's hard to believe .
That "
an old lady could do something like this to two adults .
I guess when the doctor arrives ,
apart from bringing supplies to treat the wounded ,
he 'll tell us what 's going on .
We 're locked in here , the police are outside , we can 't get out ,
we have no explanations . They know these men are here ,
and we have to get them out soon . They 've lost a lot of blood .
I can 't do anything else .
Stay with them . Thanks .
We 're going to keep on interviewing . If you don 't like something
you can out . OK ?
I would like you to tell us
what 's happened this evening ,
what 's gone on .
I can 't say too much because I was sleeping .
I heard loud screams .
Of course I woke him up , threw on what clothes I could ,
and came down here .
I have to change my clothes , I can 't ..
Something strange is going on .
Someone did something , that 's why we 're looked in here .
This building has always been ...
- Wait ! Can I talk ? - Why can 't I say it ?
There 's something ...
Yes , someone said that there was a ...
- An office , a window ... - I don 't know what it 's called .
A ... That there was a ...
what they used to do when there were atomic bombs .
- A BNC protocol . - A refuge or something .
It 's chaos .
If we knew that when you got here , we would have said :
Look , this is what happened . Let everyone know .
- But we have no idea . - But , in summary ...
Fireman , fireman , yes ...
Fireman fell ! Fireman fell !
- He fell and left ... - Fell from where ?
From up there ... up , yes .
- You were saying ? - He fell from above .
From where ?
Where ? I don 't know .
But from above , right ? I don 't know .
- From the stairwell ? - Yes .
Stairwell like this and ...
he fell in the middle . Yes .
Pablo , is this OK or should I sit lower ?
At her level .
What 's your name ? I want everyone to know .
- Jennifer . - What a beautiful name , Jennifer !
- How old are you ? - Seven .
She just had her birthday .
Great . So what happened ? Are you sick ?
Yes .
We know you can 't take your medicine , right ?
Why not ?
Because my husband isn 't allowed in .
Please do not speak right now ,
only the girl is in the shot and ...
- Sorry . - Since there is no microphone ,
we can 't hear your voice and everything gets messed up .
We 'll interview you later , OK ?
You don 't have to ...
So , besides your father ...
Who do you live with ?
With my mommy , my daddy
and my dog , Max .
Your dog isn 't here either , right ? I can 't see him .
No , he 's not .
- Do you love your dog ? - Yes .
Why isn 't he here ?
He 's at the vet .
- What 's wrong with him ? - He got sick .
I knew something would happen sooner or later .
A fire or something serious .
There must be something upstairs .
If not , I don 't get why people fall like that ...
they fall down through the stairwell , bleeding all over .
I can 't go up to my house .
So , here we are .
I am going to sue .
I am definitely going to sue .
I 'm going to call the newspapers ,
and have them write about what happened .
From the beginning until the very end .
- Cesar ? - Hello .
Hi . Sorry , but could I ask you a few questions ?
Wait ... OK , yes .
We want to cover the story .
- Are you recording already ? - No .
- OK , rolling . - Wait , I 'll sit like this .
If you prefer one side in particular ...
Have you lived here for long ?
Yes , I used to live with my mom . She died , so now I live alone .
It 's the Chinese .
They eat raw .
Raw fish . It smells ...
They always leave the door open .
I don 't know why .
I mean , if they were the nice kind that do Feng Shui
and cool stuff ... But no .
They come in and out screaming in Chinese all the time ,
in Japanese , I don 't know . Something I don 't understand .
When are we starting ?
- We did . - Why didn 't you tell me ?
Don 't you see my face is shiny ?
I think this profile 's better , right ?
- Yes . Great . - Like this , Pablo ?
Good .
OK , silence please .
Silence . Ma 'am .
- I just spoke to them outside . - It 's about time !
They told me the health inspector is on his way in .
- Health inspector ? - Yes .
There is a possible infection in the building .
An infection ?
Yes , but please calm down .
They 're just going to take blood samples
of all the residents to clarify things .
- Only of the residents ? - No , of everyone here .
When they see everything 's OK ,
they 'll let us out .
- Great . - We ask you to cooperate .
We 're going to check
if everyone is here .
A simple " here " will be fine , OK ?
Let 's start .
The main floor on the left is the office where we were before .
Who lives in the apartment on the right ?
That 's the Colombian girl 's apartment .
First floor , right ...
That 's where Mrs. lzquierdo lives , right ?
- First floor , left ? - Me .
Me , my daughter and my husband who 's been outside for a long time .
Yes , we know , lady . Calm down .
- Second floor , left ? - Us .
- You ? - No , we 're the third .
- No , we live ... - Do you or don 't you ?
- Third ... - We live on the second .
- I 'm lost . - Calm down , sir , you 're tired .
Second , left .
- Yes . Second , right ? - Present .
- Third , left ? - Here .
- Third , right ? - Yes , that 's us !
- You three ? - No , four of us .
- Four ? - My father .
- Your father ? - He upstairs .
- Where is he ? - He on bed .
My father sick .
What she means is he 's old and paralytic .
- Exactly , my father is sick . - Maybe all this is his fault .
Listen up !
We 're going to finish .
Does anyone live in the penthouse ?
No , nobody lives there .
A man from Madrid owns it , but he 's never there .
It 's been closed up for years .
Excuse me ?
- My father come down , yes ? - That 's not a good idea ,
what if he 's the cause of all this .
My father 's sick !
- He has to come down here with us . - I don 't understand you .
Be respectful , just calm down .
Your child is sick too and ...
My daughter has tonsilitis !
Nobody move until the doctor says so .
We 're going in . Don 't open the door until we say so .
Wait .
Go ahead , 341 .
OK , over .
What 's this ?
They 'll keep telling us nothing 's wrong , right ?
Pablo , I 'm going in .
- OK . - As we ...
As we were told , the health inspector is in the building .
There are incredible security measures in place .
We know nothing ,
they haven 't told us a thing .
We saw Special Forces , health inspectors
wearing suits and masks
and it 's not very comforting .
That 's all we know .
Take me to them . The rest stay here .
What is a TV crew doing here ?
Jennifer ! Don 't touch that .
- Why ? - Because I say so .
Pablo , can you come here ?
Thanks . What a pain in the ass .
Don 't you think this inspection has to do with that old lady ?
I don 't know .
The policeman and the fireman have been bitten .
If it 's contagious , they could react like the old lady .
Don 't scare me ...
Fuck , what a day .
Pablo , grab the camera . I can 't sit here doing nothing .
It 's recording ... and the lens is dirty .
Someone 's been messing around here .
It doesn 't matter . Let 's try to get something .
Shit !
Come here .
There . Look .
Hold this .
Be careful , Pablo .
Give it to me .
Can you see anything ?
What can you see ?
- They 're handcuffing him . - Who ?
Pablo , what can you see ?
Tell me what you see !
Say something !
- What are they saying ? - I can 't hear them .
- What 's that ? - What ?
I don 't know . The doctor has something in his hands .
- It 's a needle . - What 's he doing ?
- I don 't know . Wait . - What are they doing , Pablo ?
They 're injecting the fireman with something .
Pablo !
More handcuffs .
- Holy shit ! - What 's going on ?
Shit !
What 's that , Pablo ?
Say something ! What 's going on in there ?
Why are they screaming ?
Pablo , answer me !
Go , go . Run !
- What 's going on in there ? - Go , go !
What 's going on ?
What are you doing ? Guillem 's in there .
Guillem 's still in there !
He got bitten , we can 't let him out .
- What are you talking about ? - He didn 't bite me !
It spreads through saliva .
We can 't risk letting him out .
We don 't know if he 's been bitten !
The infected ones are handcuffed .
Just stay away from them .
Infected with what ?
- What 's going on ? - A minute ago they were fine !
What the fuck is all this about ?
The reaction time depends on the blood type . We can 't predict ...
Fuck ! Hurry up ! Run !
Come on , hurry up !
Now tell us what the hell is going on here .
- I 'm not authorised . - No change .
I just killed a cop who tried to bite us .
Tell us everything you know .
OK .
Yesterday we received
a call from a vet
who had a dog brought in with an unknown disease .
The dog went into a coma
and a few moments later came to
and was extraordinarily aggressive .
He started attacking all of the pets at the clinic .
We had to give him several tranquilizers
and then put him to sleep .
We followed the chip in his ear which led us to this building .
- Was the dog called Max ? - Yes .
She only has tonsilitis .
- Bullshit , tonsilitis . - Relax , ma 'am ...
We just have to be sure .
Calm down .
It 's just tonsilitis .
We think the dog spread the infection
through his saliva .
If that 's true ...
Handcuffs ! Get the handcuffs !
- Hold her ! - Jennifer !
Jennifer !
The cuffs !
Relax , we 'll get her .
Father downstairs . My father come down !
- What father ? - Her father 's sick in bed .
And you didn 't tell me ?
We can 't have infected people loose out there .
We gave you specific orders to get everyone together downstairs .
We had no idea . We thought everyone was here .
Take this . Get her and inject her with this .
Everyone must come down here .
Get this on tape !
Be careful , Pablo !
Jennifer ?
What the hell is that ?
Fucking hell !
- The old lady isn 't there . - Neither is the other one .
Jennifer ?
Jennifer .
There 's no one here . Wait .
She 's over there . Look !
Fuck !
Jennifer , relax .
Relax .
Give me the needle . The needle !
- Are you sure ? - Yes .
Be careful , man .
Jennifer .
Relax .
Give me your hand .
- Be careful . - Give me your hand .
What happened to her eyes ?
Shit !
Be careful !
Shit ! Get out of the way !
She bit me ! Get out of here !
She bit me , can 't you see ?
Go , for fuck 's sake !
Go !
Let 's go !
No down !
Don 't go down there !
They 're getting away !
Help me !
Take these off of me !
- Don 't touch me ! - Son of a bitch !
Take them off !
I don 't have it .
I don 't have the key !
What do you mean ?
- The policeman has it . - Fuck !
- The shutter ! - We 've got to get this woman out of here .
Help !
Help , you bastard !
Don 't go !
Get away !
We have to get her out of here .
- Let 's go . - No !
I 'm sorry !
Don 't leave me here !
This way , come on .
Hurry UP !
The lock !
It looks like they 're leaving .
They 're going upstairs .
- Were you bitten ? - No .
- Angela ? - No .
- You ? - No .
- Did you find the little girl ? - Who cares about the girl ?
It 's out of control .
Pablo , what the hell were they doing to that woman ?
They were eating her alive , Manu . What the hell is this ?
I don 't know !
They could all be infected by now .
- We have to get out of here . - I 'm not moving !
No ! We can stay here
until they come to get us . These things ...
No one 's going to come get us !
'Yes ! " Open Veur fu . Ckmg eyes !
They don 't give a shit ! They 're going to let us die here !
But the doctor does matter to them .
- They 'll come get the doctor . - The doctor ? Why ?
- He is in there . - Son of a bitch !
- Where ? - There !
I 'm gonna kill you !
I 've been bitten . Go away .
Get lost .
I 've been bitten !
Get back !
Go away !
Shit , shit ...
The door won 't hold .
- Go away . - Son of a bitch !
Get us out of here !
Stand away from the windows !
We repeat : Stay away from the windows
or we will be forced to take drastic measures .
Follow the inspector 's instructions .
There might be a way out .
Pablo , there might be a way out !
Listen !
There 's an underground storage area in the workshop
that has a drain cover that joins up with the sewers .
Can you hear me ?
- In the workshop there 's a basement ... - Are you sure ?
Yes , we can escape through there . The problem is the reinforced door .
- How the hell will we open it ? - With the key !
The intern is in charge . He has all the keys .
- Where ? - In his apartment .
Let 's go ! Let 's go !
He 's been bitten !
Hurry UP !
They 're not there .
Manu , we have to find the way out . We need the storage key .
Yeah , but ... how ?
The intern has the key , but we don 't know where he lives .
You checked the list !
- I can 't remember . - Pablo ?
I don 't remember either .
Manu , think . I 'm sure you can remember .
- I can 't remember ! - Think , Manu !
Guillem ! The mailboxes !
He 's called Guillem ...
Downstairs , quick ! Angela , hurry up !
Hurry UP !
Guillem Marimén , third floor , No. 2 !
She 's cuffed . We can get by .
We have to go upstairs .
Upstairs !
Be careful , Angela !
Pablo , help me !
Wait . OK .
Drop her .
- I got bitten ! - No , you didn 't .
I saw it . You didn 't .
Let 's go upstairs . Pablo , help .
- Come on , get up . - I got bitten !
You did not , Angela . I saw it , you didn 't .
Let 's go , Pablo ! Hurry up !
Hurry UP !
Shit !
- The light ! - Where 's the switch ?
- On the wall ! - I can 't find it !
- Pablo , the spotlight ! Turn it on ! - I 'm trying !
Quickly !
Move it ! Move it !
Shit ! Go upstairs , hurry !
The mallet , Angela !
Go upstairs , quickly !
It 's here .
Move .
Hurry up . I 'll wait here .
I 'll look in the living room .
Where are they ?
Look in the drawers .
Where the hell are they ?
We have to get out .
- Here , here ! - Shit , where are they ?
Shit !
The keys ...
Where are ...
The keys !
Which ones are they ?
I don 't know . Grab them all .
Let 's go .
Where 's Manu ?
Upstairs , run !
Go to the penthouse ! The key must be in the bunch .
Come on , Angela !
Which one is it ?
This one !
- Turn on the spotlight . - I can 't !
- The light is loose . - Fix it , Pablo !
I 'm trying !
They 're leaving .
- Pablo , turn it on ! - Calm down .
This is the apartment that was closed up .
- No one will be in here . - Turn it on , please .
OK .
- Where are we ? - I don 't know .
What the hell is all this ?
Pablo , over here .
Where ?
Holy shit !
- What does this mean ? - I don 't know .
- Pablo ! - What ?
" The Vatican is investigating ...
the possible possession of a Portuguese girl . "
PORTUGAL IS MOVED BY THE CASE OF THE POSSESSED GIRL
- Fuck " . - The possessed girl .
THE MEDEIROS CASE ON HOLD
Pablo , look !
It 's the same girl !
What the hell is this ?
It 's all about the same girl .
" The hospital denies releasing the girl who disappeared in the night "
Pablo !
Calm down .
It must be the pipes .
Calm down , we 'll find a way out .
We have to get out of here .
Be careful . Stay close .
Didn 't they say no one lived here ?
Calm down .
Pablo .
Over here .
What 's that ?
They 're also talking about the same thing .
What the hell is this ?
- Angela , let 's go . - Wait !
It must have something to do with ...
Look !
A tape recorder .
- There 's no electricity . - It 's off .
There .
I 've finally isolated the enzyme .
The problem is that it 's unstable .
It deteriorates when it comes into contact with oxygen .
I am , however , optmistic .
If all goes well we 'll have a vaccine soon .
The analyses were successful .
What the hell is he talking about ?
Something unexpected has happened .
The enzyme is not only resistant but has mutated .
It behaves much like the flu .
This leads us to a horrible conclusion .
It might be contagious .
I don 't get it .
The telegram from Rome has arrived .
The Medeiros girl must die .
He 's talking about the girl , Pablo .
She was here .
I must eliminate her and erase all signs of her existence .
What the hell is this guy saying ?
Finally my prayers have been answered .
We have to get out of here .
This decision should have been made years ago .
This has all been a big mistake .
I must follow the procedures .
The ritual is very specific .
Come here . Stay close .
I 'm going to seal off the room .
The seal should keep her in .
If anything goes wrong , may God help us .
Wait .
- I 'm going to look . - No !
There might be a way out through the attic .
- We have to give it a try . - What are you going to do ?
I 'll record what 's up there and we can look at it .
Pablo . Bring the camera down .
There are really weird noises .
- What happened ? - Something hit the camera .
Turn it on .
The fucking light broke !
- Turn it on , Pablo ! - I can 't , it 's busted .
- Fuck ! What now ? - Relax . Don 't move .
I 'll turn on the night vision .
OK , I can see you now .
That 's good .
Stick your hand out .
- I can 't see you . Where are you ? - OK , I got you .
Relax , it 's me .
I can see if I use the camera .
Get behind me and don 't let go .
We 'll be OK . We 're going to get out .
I 'll find the way out .
Don 't let go , OK ?
- Stay still . - Why ?
There 's something . Go back .
Don 't make a sound .
Get down .
Keep quiet , for God 's sake !
It can 't see us . If it can 't hear us , it won 't find us .
Let 's go .
- Run ! - Pablo !
Run !
Answer me ! I can 't hear you !
Pablo .
We have to tape everything , Pablo . For fuck 's sake .